本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 小癫羊 涕涕真是naive 许块块
校对： 许块块   后期： 唱唱反调
大家好 我是安娜・斯科
Hi everyone. I'm Anna Silk.
欢迎来到俱乐部
And welcome to the Clubhouse.
我和妖女迷行的主创团队在此
I'm here with the Lost Girl cast and we're getting ready for
一小时内将开始第四季的首映
the premiere of season 4, in just under an hour.
我们将会回答粉丝的问题
We're gonna be answering fan questions and chatting about
也会聊聊生活 播放一些网络视频短片
life and having a little movie night and viewing the webisodes.
让大家来介绍一下自己吧
So let's have everyone introduce themselves.
嗨 我是里克・赫兰德 我饰演特里克
Hi. I'm Rick Howland. I play Trick.
我是保罗・阿莫斯 我饰演伐克斯
I'm Paul Amos. And I play Vex.
我是瑞秋・司德腾 我饰演塔米辛
I'm Rachel Skarsten. I play Tamsin.
我是柯辛娜・索罗 我饰演肯吉
I'm Ksenia Solo, and I play Kenzi.
我是克里斯・海罗里德 我饰演戴森
Kris Holden-Ried. Dyson.
我是祖伊・巴莫我饰演劳伦・路易斯医生
I'm Zoie Palmer, and I play Dr. Lauren Lewis.
我是K.c. 柯林斯 我饰演黑尔
And I'm K.C. Collins, and I play Hale.
我是安娜 我饰演波
And I'm Anna, and I play Bo.
自从第三季结束后已经有一段时间了
It's been a while since season 3.
所以让我们回顾一下 看看第三季的结尾吧
So let's take a look back and see where we left off.
我会像他一样统治
I will reign as he did.
即使死亡也会畏惧我们
Even death will fear us.
只有我才能选择谁将生存
Only I will choose who lives.
这只是短暂的分开...
This is just a break...
对吗?
right?
不 请告诉我她不是那位
No. Please tell me she's not the one.
上次你给人类做手术是什么时候?
When was the last time you actually operated on a human?
放松 这是你人类的最后时刻
Relax. It's the last time you'll be human.
我倡议投一次对假阿什的不信任票
I call for a vote of no confidence in this fake Ash.
莫里根刚刚宣布你是他们领地的敌人
The Morrigan just declared you an enemy of the realm.
在你安全之前 我不会离开你
I'm not leaving your side 'til you're safe.
你很坚强 肯吉 但终究是人类
You're tough, Kenzi, but you're human.
就快不是了
Not for long.
- 我们总有一天会死去 - 停车
- We all gotta die someday. - Stop the car.
谢谢刚刚的飙车戏份了哈
Thanks for going all Thelma and Louise on me there, 'Ach.
知道吗 没什么比开车翻下悬崖更好看的了
You know? Never looked better going off a cliff.
上一季发生了很多事啊
A lot happened last season,
对不对伙计们
huh, guys?
是啊 上一季的确发生了很多
Yes, a lot did happen last season.
比如呢?
Like what?
我生了个儿子叫山姆
Including the birth of my son, Sam.
跟妖女迷行大家庭 分享喜悦真是太棒了
It's been great to share this time with my Lost Girl family.
每个人都很欢迎山姆
Everyone has welcomed Sam,
他也是第四季的重要部分
and he's been a big part of season 4.
我也想把他介绍给大家
And I just wanted to introduce him to you guys.
但已经过了山姆的睡觉时间
But it is just past Sam's bedtime,
所以他要去睡觉了
so he's going to go off to sleep now.
好吧 晚安 山姆
So, good night, Sam.
- 晚安 山姆 - 晚安 伙计
- Good night, Sam. - Good night, buddy.
现在 我认为你们肯定同意我的看法
Now, I think you guys would definitely agree with me when
那就是我们拥有全世界最棒的粉丝 对不对?
I say that we have the greatest fans in the world. Right?
是啊 - 我确信
Yes. - Bet it.
事实上我们拥有一个神奇的
We actually have a magical
写满了粉丝们问题的异种之箱
Fae box full of questions that you guys have written in with.
所以 来看看你们都想知道什么吧
So, let's see what you all want to know.
第一个问题 来自妮基・克莱尔
First question, from Nicky Claire.
"你们在哪长大 小时候是什么样?"
"Where did you grow up and what were you like as a kid?"
- 哦哦 - 从你开始吧 K.c.
- Ooh. Ah. - Let's start with you, K.C.
我绝大部分时间在多伦多长大
I grew up in... for the most part, Toronto.
很多地方 但是我不想说的那么复杂
A lot of other places, but to keep it nice and not
所以就是多伦多吧 我小的时候...
complicated, Toronto. And as a kid, I was...
我是说 我很健壮
I mean, I was athletic...
我觉得我是整个宇宙的守卫者
I felt like I was a defender of the universe.
- 真不错 - 哇哦 - 我守护着许多人
- Nice. - Wow. - I defended a lot of people.
结果我打了不少架 我的祖母对此很不乐意
And I ended up in a lot of fights that my Grandma wasn't happy about.
- 祖伊 你呢? - 我在坎波恩长大
- What about you, Zoe? - I grew up in Camborne,
英国的康沃尔郡 直到我十岁才搬过来
Cornwall, England, until I was about ten, and then we moved here.
并且我十分亢奋 好像我是个超级小孩
And I was hyper. Like, I was a really hyper kid.
别忘了 祖伊 你和我住在同一个村庄
on't forget, Zoie, you lived in the same village as me, too.
在威尔士? 我也住在威尔士
In Wales? I lived in Wales, too.
- 你们住在村庄里 - 是啊
- You guys lived in a village. - Yeah.
是的 一个很小很小的村庄
Yeah, a tiny, little village.
我是个城里人 我喜欢...
I'm a city boy. I like...
我在新不伦瑞克省的弗雷德里顿长大
I grew up in Fredericton, New Brunswick.
我知道
I know this.
我喜欢什么呢?
And what was I like?
我觉得我当时和现在没什么两样
I was kind of exactly like I am now, I think.
但是我的确花了一整个夏天扮成神奇女侠
But I did spend an entire summer dressed as Wonder Woman,
逐个打击我们社区的犯罪
literally fighting crime in my neighbourhood.
- 真的吗 - 当然了
- Really? - Yes.
我每天都穿同样的衣服
I wore same thing every day.
架打的怎么样?
How was that one fight?
得了吧 那可是新不伦瑞克省
Come on, it's New Brunswick. Come on.
那也会发生许多案件的
Hey, some stuff happens there, okay.
很奇怪 我长大了还会扮演神奇女侠
Strangely enough, I grew up also playing Wonder Woman.
所以我带着手环到处走
So I would walk around with my bracelets.
你是认真的吗?
Are you being serious?
是啊 我很认真的 我爱神奇女侠
Yes, I am. I loved Wonder Woman.
我在拉脱维亚的里加长大
Me, I grew up in Riga, Latvia.
小时候 我只记得我超爱童话故事
As a kid, I just remember loving fairy tales.
没有比听故事更好的事了
There was nothing better than being told a story.
所以这就是我当演员的原因吧
So I think that's why I wanted to become an actor,
因为我太热爱叙事艺术了
because I just loved the art of storytelling so much.
- 瑞秋呢? - 你就是从那起步的
- Rachel? - That's where you started it.
我在加拿大的多伦多长大
I grew up in Toronto, Canada.
我还是孩子时 我确实很有女孩样
And as a little girl, I was very much a girly girl.
所有东西都是粉色的
Everything was pink.
是啊 我知道 很震惊吧
Yeah, I know. Shocking.
我曾经很有女孩样 因为我现在就是个爷们
I was a girly girl. 'Cause I'm like a dude now, you know? So...
- 闭嘴吧 - 你呢 保罗?
- Shut up. - How about you, Paul?
好吧 我在威尔士的一个小村庄里长大
Well, I grew up in a little village in Wales where we used
我们惯说一点当地语言 就是威尔士语
to speak a little funny hobbit language called Welsh.
当我说威尔士语的时候 听起来就像这样
If I were to speak Welsh then it would sound something like this.
所以这是门美丽的语言
So it's a beautiful language,
被许多美丽的人讲出来
surrounded by beautiful people
还有一个美丽的乡村
and beautiful countryside,
我在那里长大真是非常非常幸运
and I was very, very lucky to grow up there.
那你怎么会变得这么邪恶?
And how did you turn out to be so evil?
不 我要告诉你发生了什么
No. I tell you what happened.
我的祖父是个主持人 就像酒吧的司仪一样
My Grandfather was a compere, which is like an MC in the clubs.
所以他经常在酒吧里唱歌讲笑话来逗大家
So he used to entertain and sing and tell jokes in the clubs.
我的叔叔经常偷偷带我去酒吧
And my uncles used to smuggle me into the clubs.
所以我可以坐在桌子上
So I could sit on the table
看我祖父逗笑400多人
and watch my Grandfather entertain like 400 people.
你呢 ?
How about you, Rickster?
我在安大略省的金斯顿长大
I was born in Kingston, Ontario,
就挨着马路 我是个刻薄的孩子
just down the road. And I was a sarcastic child,
有点博学多才 所以 你们懂的 就这样
a bit of a know-it-all. So, you know, there you go.
完美啊 看看命运...
Perfect. Look what fate...
我没有脱离轨迹
I didn't fall far from the tree.
没脱离我角色的轨迹
From my character's tree.
下一个问题 来自福尔・凯斯费
Next question, from "Val Kensfey."
"剧中的所有虚构生物中
"Of all the mythological creatures that have been on the
如果你有机会 最想成为哪一种?"
show, which one would you want to be if you had the chance?
- 沼泽怪 - 沼泽怪?
- The swamp one. - The swamp one?
你想住在沼泽中?
You wanna live in a swamp?
又泥泞又冷又潮湿?
Muddy and cold and wet?
带着那样的脑袋?
With the head?
瑞秋的品味很古怪的
Rachel's got a weird taste in things.
外表超级诡异 出来的时候哇哇大叫
It's just to get to look like that and come out be like, "Waah!"
好吧 伙计们 让我们看看粉丝的视频提问
Okay, guys, let's check out a fan video question.
来自奥德利
This is from Audrey.
专业地说
Professionally talking,
推特是不是带来了改变?
did Twitter change something,
如果是 改变了什么
and if yes, what?
还有:我爱你们
PS: I love you guys.
- 我们也很爱你 奥德利 - 是啊
- We love you too, Audrey. - Yeah.
谢谢你的问题和一直的支持
Thanks for your question and your endless support.
她是从一开始就关注我们的铁杆粉丝
She's been one of our biggest fans from the very beginning.
我认为她是本剧成功的原因
I think she's the reason the show is successful.
- 只靠一人之力 - 你知道什么最疯狂吗
- Single-handedly. - Do you know what has been
就是发推特的人有好多啊
crazy, though, is how big Twitter has become now, and the fact
其实 上一季的首映 就上了热门讨论榜首
that on the last season premiere, it was trending #1.
我记得很清楚我当时坐在哪
And I remember exactly where I was sitting.
我就想看看热门讨论
And I'm like, I'm gonna see what's trending.
"妖女迷行? 什么?!"
"Lost Girl? What?!"
然后我给我认识的每个人打电话 我就说
And then just called everybody I knew. I was like, "You have
"现在马上看推特 去推特上"
to go on Twitter right now. Go on Twitter."
太疯狂了 真是件大事
And that was wild. It was really huge.
这是我们观众和粉丝的证明
It's a testament to our viewers and our fans.
好吧 我们现在要休息一下 看一段网络视频
Okay, we're going to take a break for a webisode now.
在第三季最后 肯吉和布鲁斯
At the end of season 3, Kenzi and Bruce sped off in
在一辆非常性感的车中疾驰 找寻
a very sexy car, in search of Massimo.
我想知道 这两个人的公路奔驰
I wonder, what would a road trip
会是什么样子并且
with these two be like, besides
他们还吃了很多奇多 听着辣妹组合的音乐
eating lots of Cheetos and listening to Spice Girls?
让我们拭目以待
Let's check it out.
布鲁斯 谈话终止吧
End of discussion, Brucey.
我和我想要的东西仅一桥之隔
I am one bridge away from getting what I need.
不成功便成仁
Strew it or bust.
但是肯吉 马西莫不是个好人
But Kenzi, Massimo is not a nice person.
别说了! 好人就像又脏又旧的牛仔裤
Please! Nice is yesterday's skinny jeans.
我需要的是今日的残酷真相
What Kenzi needs is today's brutal truth.
真相就是异种末日到了
And the truth is that it's Fae-mageddon out there.
所以我需要穿上盔甲 异种的盔甲
So I need to armour up, Fae style,
把那些人类的巧舌之徒抛开一会
lose this human shrike for a while...
但是我是异种 我的生命并非完美无缺
But I'm Fae, and my life is not exactly peaches and cream.
好吧 至少你还存在着 而我...
Well, at least you've got presence. Me...
哦 你看到了吗 我几乎都不能走路
Oh! You see? I can barely even walk.
- 是因为你的鞋太高了 - 真的吗?
- That's your shoes. They're too tall. - Really?
在你我经历这一切之后 你还羞辱我的鞋?
After everything you and I have been through, you're dissing my kicks?
羞辱? 我从不羞辱什么
Diss? I never diss.
- 哦! - 我甚至不知道怎么羞辱别人
- Oh! - I don't even know how to diss.
肯吉 等等 有危险 到处都是危险
Kenzi, wait. Danger. It's everywhere.
- 不许过 - 谁说的?
- Passage denied. - Says who?
- 数六下 - 数七...下
- Up your six. - Up yours... seven.
那是我的口号 眼线妹 你根本不懂
That's my handle, eyeliner. You probably wouldn't understand.
你需要男人告诉你怎么做
You're used to men telling you how it is.
男人 算了 男孩 甭想
Men, nyet. Boys, never.
尤其不需要这种卷发 磕碜的臆想狂
Especially not scruffy, pit-stained maggots.
抱歉 你这身上世纪的破布太吵了
Sorry, your trashcan goth rags are screaming '90s too loud.
- 我听不见你说的! - 哦 真的吗
- I can't hear you! - Oh, really?
好吧 如果你不懂潮流的话 我很遗憾
Well, I'm sorry if you can't stand style,
你个主流嬉皮士爱好者 滚吧
you mainstream hipster poser. Then get off the runway.
天啊 碰上巨怪了
Oh boy. We'd better troll.
我没跟你说话 什么
You I'm not talking to. But if I was, I'd be like,
像桥下的巨怪吗?
what, like an under-the-bridge fugly troll?
不 网络巨怪
No. An Internet troll.
他们真的是巨怪?
Those are, like, actual trolls?
- 啊哦 - 天啊
- Uh-huh. - Oh boy.
嘿 小六 你不应该在网上烦人么
Hey, Six, shouldn't you be online pissing people off?
我匿名损人太过了
I trolled a little bit too awesomely on Anonymous.
我们发现了我 转移我一个月
They had me hacked, transferred for a month.
来了老式桥哈 活该
Mmm. To old-time Bridgeville. Well, bam.
用阿兰尼斯的不朽名言就是 太讽刺了吧
In the immortal words of my girl Alanis, isn't it ironic.
我只剩一周的时间了 好吗
I only have a week left, okay?
你要哭了吗 你想让我帮忙吗
Are you gonna cry? Do you want me to polish up
帮你抛光那些巴迪霍利镜片?
those non-prescription Buddy Holly glasses for you?
哦 你很犀利 也很聪明
Oh, you're sharp. And smart.
还很淘气
And nasty.
来吧伙计们 这样对抗着让我手都痒了
Come on, guys. Confrontation makes me itchy.
让我们重新开始 我是
Let's start over. I'm Bruce.
- 布鲁斯- 很高兴见到你 布鲁斯
- Bruce. - Nice to meet you, Bruce.
这么瘦骨嶙峋 还这么能打
Oh, for a skinny guy, you sure pack a lotta punch.
是啊 巨怪嘛
Yeah. Troll.
你瞧 我需要在桥那边找德鲁人
Look. I need to get to a Druid on the other side of that bridge,
穿过那个你守卫的桥
the bridge that you've been assigned to guard.
什么代价啊 百事通?
What of it, Captain Exposition?
好吧 怎么做才行?
Okay, how's this gonna work?
你想要什么报酬 我的头发?
Do you want some kind of payment, a lock of my hair?
当成牙线用一个星期吗?
And me flossing weave for my teeth for a week?
不了 谢谢
No thank you.
是啊 如果你吃东西的话
Yeah, if you were eating it.
哦 天哪 你要吃了我吗?
Oh, my god, are you gonna eat me?
如果你在这签字 我就放过你
Not if you sign here.
什么 你想让我守卫这座桥?
What, you want me to take over guarding the bridge?
你再合适不过了 你骂人和我一样损
You're perfect for the gig. You spit back insults as fast as I do.
不过你仅剩一周啊
Yeah, but you have, like, a week left.
所以没什么大不了嘛
Exactly. So it's no biggie.
就跟你化眼妆的时间一样长嘛
What's that, as long as it takes you to apply your eye makeup?
我需要马上见到马西莫
I need to see Massimo now.
除非你在这签名
Not until you sign here.
看我的完美嘴型 不
Read my perfectly lined lips. No.
好吧 没事 没事的
Okay. It's okay. It's all right.
别哭啦 没事的
Don't cry. It's all right.
小六子 我又没说什么 先冷静
Six, honey, I don't speak sad troll. Just slow down.
冷静 深呼吸 告诉肯吉怎么回事
Slow down, take a breath and tell Kenzi correct what's wrong.
是这样的 一个月前
Well, see, it was about a month ago
我在网上遇到一个叫欧文的人
I was online and I met this guy named Owen,
明天应该是我们第一次约会
and tomorrow was supposed to be our first, like, date
在一个咖啡馆兼游戏室兼折纸室的地方
at this coffee shop/game room/ Origami workshop.
噢 红色康乃馨 这样他就能认出你了
Oh, the red carnation so he knows it's you.
很传统嘛 我喜欢
Old-school. I like it.
但糟的是时间定在两点
But it's suck-atood central.
好嘛 但是我不能擅离职守
Okay? Because I can't leave the bridge unguarded.
无所谓了 我不损人
It doesn't even matter. I can't talk to anyone
都没法好好说话了
without insulting them, road-trip breath.
- 对吧 - 好吧
- See? - Okay.
你喜欢黑别人因为这样显得自己聪明
You like insulting people because you think you're clever.
- 我就是天才 笨蛋 - 哼
- I am clever, no lobes. - Uh-huh.
那你干嘛不花点心思说点好话出来 试试看
So why don't you try being clever by saying something nice? Try me.
看到你的裤子我不想吐
Your pants don't even make me wanna puke.
好吧 首战告捷
Okay. Great first try.
但是注意不要说呕吐了 再试试 当我是欧文
But let's pin the puke and try again. I'm Owen.
你网上的切格瓦拉名言集
Your online collection of Che Guevara quotes
让我想给自己织个贝雷帽
make me want to knit my own beret.
棒 棒 超棒 太好了
Yes! Yes. Totally. Okay.
那关于这个桥
So, about the bridge...
没办法姐就是这么有爱
I am such a sucker for love.
- 不要签 - 少管闲事
- No! - Mind your own business.
她的事就是我的事 你这个傻叉小网迷
Kenzi is my business, you Internet cockroach shag rag.
- 布鲁斯 没事的 - 而你
- Bruce, it's okay. - And you,
- 你真是一点都不知道
you have some deep-seated misconceptions
自己多么渺小脆弱
about just how little power you have over people.
但你是我朋友 所以我支持你
But you're my friend, and I support you
尽管你穿这鞋连路都走不了
even if your shoes are ridiculously road-trip unfriendly.
哇 他真棒 和网上的水军一样棒
Oh, he's good. Like, online board message good.
- 是啊 谁会想到啊 - 我也不想这样
- Yeah. Who knew? - I don't like being this person.
但为了让你开心 快把合约给我吧
But I'll do it if it makes you happy. So just give me the contract.
噢 太感谢你了 兄弟 能握个手吗
Ohh, thanks, dude. Can I shake your hand?
我能捏碎吗
Can I crush it?
祝我好运吧 还有 大爱这鞋子 超炫的
Wish me luck. PS. Love the shoes. Fierce!
谢啦 祝你好运 玩的开心哦
Thanks! Good luck! Have fun!
我爱你 小肯
I love you, Kenzi.
- 但如果你发生什么事 - 闭嘴啦
- But if anything happened... - Shut up.
- 你才闭嘴 - 你闭嘴
- You shut up. - You shut your mouth.
- 你走开 - 你关门滚粗
- You shut your face. - Shut the front door.
你走的时候别被门夹到哦
Don't let it hit you on the ass on the way out.
哇!
Bam!
谢谢你替我守桥 为我做的一切
Thank you for guarding this bridge, for everything.
感谢你的出现
Thanks for being you.
- 别轻信马西莫 - 我答应你
- Don't trust Massimo. - Promise.
不要怀疑大块头的智慧
They never suspect the big ones.
- 大爱啊 - 超棒的
- Love it! - Awesome!
这段关系很有爱 我喜欢看他们在一起
It's a nice relationship. I love seeing them together,
因为我感觉他们都在寻找自己的栖身之地
because I feel like they're both looking for their place in the world.
我觉得肯吉同情布鲁斯
And I think Kenzi feels bad that Bruce has had this really hard
的坎坷的命运 所以和他感同身受
life and hard upbringing, so she relates to him.
所以我觉得这段关系很赞
So, I think it's a beautiful friendship.
好啦 同志们 我们先休息一下
Okay, guys, we are going to take a break.
等一下会看到更多网络剧
But when we come back, more webisodes, some
让我激动的花絮
bloopers that I'm super excited to see, and
和更多的粉丝提问 等下见啦
some more of your fan questions. So, see you soon.
大家好 我是Kc 欢迎回到俱乐部
Well, hello. I'm K.C. Welcome back to the Clubhouse.
今晚我们在此讨论妖女迷行的一切
We're here tonight talking about everything Lost Girl,
来迎接第四季首播
and to get ready for the season 4 premiere.
我们收到无数的粉丝提问
We have tons of questions from the fans.
第一个来自谢莉尔・王尔德
The first question here is from Shirley R. Wild,
这是关于安娜和祖伊的
and it's for Anna and Zoie.
两个野性的女子
Who surely are wild.
说得好 伙计 真不错 好啦
Well done, sir. Well done. Okay.
波和劳伦是两个很不同的个体
"Bo and Lauren are opposites on so many levels, yet their
但她们的爱却惊天动地 好像天生注定
love is phenomenal and inevitable."
- 嗯 - 你觉得是为什么呢
- Okay. - "Why do you think that is?"
- 反向吸引吧 - 嗯 就是这样
- Opposites attract. - Definitely there's that.
我觉得对劳伦来说 波是少数
And also, I think that for Lauren, Bo is one of the few people...
劳伦觉得自己在很多时候是个局外人
Like, Lauren I think feels like an outsider in a lot of ways because
因为她是人类 随时会被异种遗弃
she's a human and at any moment could be tossed aside by the Fae.
而波出现前就是人类
I think that because Bo comes from a world where she kind
在某种程度上来说 好像是这样
of started as a human, to some degree, or seems that way,
我们有一种 我觉得我有点依赖你
that we kind of had some... I think I clinged on to you a little bit.
我觉得不和祖伊・巴莫擦出火花真是太难了
I would find it hard to not have chemistry with Zoie Palmer,
因为她这么美丽动人冰雪聪明
because she's beautiful and smart and...
你也是啦 你也好美腻
You're those things, too. You're beautiful, too.
- 别说啦 - 快停下 不 - 你停下
- Shut up. - Stop it. - No, you shut up.
好吧 小伙伴们 不管她们了
All right, everyone, let's leave them
让她们就这样闹吧
and let them at it.
我们继续 这个问题来自丹尼尔・米勒
So, here we go. This one is from Daniel Miller.
他说很喜欢预告里的浪人这首歌
And he says, "I love the Wanderer song cover in the promo."
想知道这是从哪儿来的 他可以下载吗
He wants to know, where did it come from and can he get it?
真是个好问题 这里面有个好故事
Well, that's a good question and a good story.
因为杰・费尔斯通 我们的执行制片
Because Jay Firestone, our executive producer,
和范娜莎・皮亚拉 一个很棒的制片人
and Vanessa Piazza, one of our amazing producers,
一起面试了很多
they got together and they actually held auditions
女歌手来唱这首歌
for female vocalists to come in to cover the song.
最后选择的是名叫
And the one that won it, her name is...
- 艾米丽・摩尔来唱 - 艾米丽・摩尔
- Emily Mover. - Emily Mover. M-O-V-E-R.
可以在Showcase官网下载
And it's available on showcase.ca .
不好意思 我们能再来杯酒吗
Excuse me, can we have a another glass of that wine?
哇谢谢 布鲁斯
Ah, merci! Bruce
- 耶 布鲁斯 - 布鲁斯
- Yay, Bruce! - Bruce!
- 你好啊 波 怎么样 - 很好啊你呢
- Hi, Bo. How are you? - Good. How are you?
- 狼人
- Wolfman.
我现在比你更害怕 相信我
I'm more afraid than you are right now, trust me.
- 谁是发图小能手 - 大家来投票吧
- Who is the best Instagramer? - Oh, guys. Let's take a vote.
谁最爱发图?
Who is the best Instagramer?
我觉得一定是沙发上这三个人的一个
It's got to be one of these three, I think, on the couch.
- 因为我不玩 - 我不知道
- 'Cause I don't Instagram. - I don't know.
我高高在上 我只想说
I think I'm high up there. I just want to say.
我觉得克里斯拍的照片很艺术有美感
I feel like Kris takes phenomenally artistic, beautiful photos.
别忘了柯辛娜单人
The thing is, Ksenia Solo has entered
- 参加了摄影比赛 - 我觉得是柯辛娜
- a competition for her photographs. - I think Ksenia wins.
如果你都去参赛了
If you're entering competitions,
- 自动胜出嘛 - 是吗
- you just automatically win. - Oh, yeah?
好啦 同志们这有一个视频提问
Okay, guys, so there is another video question.
我们开始吧 开始了
Should we get to it? Let's get to it.
我们想了解大家在片场的性格
We want to know more about people's personalities on set.
比如谁最搞笑
Like, who is the funny one?
谁有公主病 从不出自己的拖车
And who is the Diva who never comes out of their trailer and
一副说别看我 别和我说话的样子
says, "Don't look at me. Don't even talk to me."
- 谁是飚戏大王 - 谁最幽默
- Who's the serious method actor? - And who is the practical joker?
我有王子病 我从不出拖车
I'm the Diva. I never leave my trailer.
- 从不 - 我缩在里面
- Never. - I huddle in there.
我真不觉得我们中谁有公主病
I don't know if any of us are Divas, really.
有些人总要花久一点时间
I mean, some of us are slower to come out of
才出拖车 但我不知道是谁
our trailers than others. I don't know who.
但你知道吗
But you know what?
男人们总是要花很久打扮
The guys always take a little extra time primping and priming.
神奇女侠才有公主病
Well, Wonder Woman is a bit of a Diva.
谁最爱搞笑
Who is a practical joker?
我觉得不是你就是克里斯
I think it's either you or Kris.
对 你和克里斯中的一个
Yeah. Between you and Kris.
我们就是常常互相搞怪
Well, we just practical-joke each other.
- 的确 - 好吧
- That's true. - Well, there you go.
克里斯拍着拍着就脱裤子
Kris does every other scene with his pants down.
- 对或者 手里拿把吉他 - 我就说
- Yeah, or a guitar in his hand. - I always say, you are
你现实中更像肯吉而不是戴森
actually more like Kenzi in your real life than you are Dyson.
所以你演肯吉 真是小菜一碟
So when you played Kenzi, it was like no biggie.
你就是这种性格的
You're used to that.
我当时就觉得 克里斯终于可以本色出演了
I was like, "Oh. Kris finally gets to play himself."
哇噢
Woo-hoo!
到时候看另一个网络剧啦
I think it's a good time for another webisode.
特里克和黑尔一直是密友
Trick and Hale have always had a very tight relationship.
今年作为新艾什 黑尔视特里克为导师
As the new Ash, this year, Hale really used Trick as a mentor.
在接下来的网络剧中有幸可以看到
This next webisode was a nice chance to see the two back
特里克回到豆吧后两人的重聚
together after Trick gets back to the Dal.
让我们来看看第二集网络剧 预言
Let's take a look at the second webisode, Prophecy.
这真像僵尸世界大战的战场
It's like World War Z happened in here.
- 欢迎回家 布拉德・皮特 - 你来干嘛
- Welcome home, Brad Pitt. - What are you doing here?
给你捎邮件 有人落在你门口了
Bring in your mail. Someone left it on your doorstep.
我在整理东西 不当艾什后
And I'm checking up on things. Being the former Ash,
我闲得很
it leaves you with a lot of free time on your hands.
不用谢我了
You're welcome.
知道我的酒吧发生什么了吗
Any idea what happened to my bar?
复仇女神闯进来开了个舞会吗
Furies broke in and threw a party?
说到舞会 你的性福之旅怎么样
Oh, speaking of partying, how was your sex-cation?
别提了
Just... don't.
不好意思 我不知道你和史黛拉分手了
Ooh. Sorry, I didn't know you and Stella split.
好吧 和我说说吧
All right, well, talk to me.
这个嘛
Well...
你听说过分离是甜蜜的忧伤吗
Do you know the saying parting is such sweet sorrow?
嗯
Yeah.
我的很甜蜜
I've had sweeter.
女人啊
Women.
嗯 还有爱女人的傻子们
Mm-hmm. And the fools who would love them.
- 还是自己的家好啊 - 所剩无几啦
- Be it ever so humble. - What's left of it.
再说到我的初恋吧
Now to tend to my first love.
我给你倒点茶
I'll make you some tea.
请告诉我你见到肯吉了
Please tell me you've seen Kenzi.
你是我第一个见到的熟人
You're the first familiar face I've seen come through that door.
她发短信说自己没事
She sent me a text message saying she was okay.
但是我不知道她在哪儿
It's just, I don't know where she is.
而戴森和塔姆辛我都不知道他们是不是还活着
Dyson and Tamsin on the other hand, I don't even know if they're alive.
我对这发生的有不好的预感
I have a bad feeling about what happened here.
备一桶酒慢慢干就会好的
Nothing a bucket and some elbow grease can't fix.
- 这是什么 - 轻拿轻放
- What's this? - Be very careful with that.
看起来像什么异种显灵板
It looks like some kind of Fae Ouija board.
这是个古老强大的占卜板
It's a very old, very powerful diviniation plank.
我刚就是这么说的啊
I believe that's what I just said.
是吗 你以为德尔菲神谕
Really? You think the Delphic oracles
就用粗直板和灵界沟通吗
used a chip board to commune with the spirit world?
这是台湾制造吗
Were there boards also made in Taiwan?
我没说这是原版的
I never said it was an original.
- 但同样威力无比 - 我赌一爪各玛币
- But no less powerful. - Well, one dragma...
你的板子预言的能力
says that your plank is as good as predicting the future
和我的八号球一样挫
as my big old eight balls.
你不能用预言赌博的
You can't gamble on prophecy.
就像用潘多拉盒子放遥控器一样
That's like using Pandora's box as handy place to keep your TV remote.
- 我就知道 - 喂
- Just what I thought. - Uh!
你想看证据么 好吧
You want proof? Fine.
- 你在干嘛啊 - 看不出来吗
- What the hell are you doing? - What's it look like?
你看起来像脑子坏了
It looks like you were dropped on your head.
- 好吧 我受够了 - 好啦 天啊
- Okay, I've had enough. - Okay. All right. Jeez.
我知道为什么史黛拉把你甩了
I'm starting to see why Stella curbed your ass.
通灵神谕是很严肃的 事先声明
Channelling the oracle is serious. And just for the record,
是我提的分手
I'm the one who did the curbing.
好啦 我会乖的
Okay, I'll behave.
闭上眼睛 清空大脑
Close your eyes. Clear your mind.
这对你倒是不难的
That shouldn't be too hard.
准备好了就提问吧
And when you're ready, ask your question.
哪位美女正想着我呢
Which fine woman is thinking about me right now?
肯吉
- 你看见了吧 - 你让板子这么做的
- You see. - You rigged the board to do that.
我怎么会知道
How would I know that?
人人都知道
Everybody knows that.
好吧 这次认真点
All right, serious question this time.
为了你的钱
To your money.
谁会接任艾什
Who will replace me as the next Ash?
黑尔?
Hale?
你当备战未来
Prepare yourselves for the arrival.
预言将会灵验
The prophesy shall be fulfilled.
枕戈待旦 严阵以待
Prepare. Prepare.
磨厉以须
Prepare.
我就知道这货是假的
Eh, I knew this thing was a fake.
跟你玩的不错
Pleasure doing business with you.
尤那达人
The Una Mens.
严阵以待
Prepare.
好嘞 不错哟
All right. There we go.
有点前传后传的意思
A little bit more back-story and pre-story.
- 算命板把我吓死了 - 我也是
- Ouija boards always freak me out. - Yeah, me too.
我们请詹姆斯・厄尔・琼斯来配音的么?
Did we hire James Earl Jones to do that voice, or...?
不 亲爱的 我只是调了个频
Well, no, baby, I just went from the diaphragm.
- 没错 他与生俱来 - 好吧 都是你
- Yeah, he just brought in. - That was all you.
- 哥就是牛 - 了解
- That's what I do. - We know it.
刚刚很棒哦
So, that was great.
我们现在要进入广告休息时间啦
We're going to go to a commercial break now.
马上回来 我们将会回答更多问题
But when we get back, we'll answer more
看到更多网络片段哦 不要走开
questions and see another webisode. So stay tuned.
- 嗨起来! - 耶!
- Go wild! - Yeah!
大家好 我是克里斯・海罗里德
Hi. I'm Kris Holden-Reid.
欢迎回来俱乐部
Welcome back to the Clubhouse,
我们在此谈论最喜爱的妖女迷行片段
where we're talking about our favourite Lost Girl stories,
网络片段 并为第四季今晚开播做准备哦
webisodes, and getting ready for the big season 4 premiere tonight.
马上要播出啦 不要走开
It's coming up very soon, so don't go anywhere, because we're
我们要回答魔力盒子中的问题啦
going to have a little bit more questions from the magic box.
- 该我抽题了吗? - 是哦
- It's my turn with the magic box. - Oh, really?
崔西・阿金斯通提问
From Tracy Atkinson,
波需要性能量维生
"Bo needs to feed off of sexual energy to survive.
如果你必须要一件物赖以为生 会是什么?
If you had to feed off of any one thing to survive, what would it be?"
- 高级披萨啊 - 我选笑容
- Any deluxe pizza. - I vote laughter.
- 怎么样? 不错吧 - 哇!
- How's that one? Right? - Whoa!
我喜欢逗人笑 他们一笑
I like making people laugh, so when they
我就可以靠他们的笑容活命
laugh, then I can feed off that laughter.
要我说 人生最动容的事莫过于
For me, nothing moves me more in life
人们真诚实在的善良
than when people are genuinely kind.
- 我要以善良为食 - 哇塞 多有深度
- So I would feed off of kindness. - See, now I've got to get all deep.
我本来想说香蕉啊 玉米煎饼什么的
I was just thinking like, a plantain, or a burrito.
- 现在我得深刻点了 - 我以意面为食
- But now I need to get all deep. - I would also feed off of pasta.
下一位莱斯利・戴米科的问题
So, next question is from Leslie dAmico.
请任意一位演员分享与粉丝们的难忘瞬间
"Can any of the actors tell us about memorable moments meeting fans?"
我觉得我们都很幸运能有
I think we've all been very lucky in terms of getting really
- 很酷的粉丝创作 海报 画作 - 是啊
- cool fan art, posters, paintings. - Yeah.
我有件很棒的要分享 我超激动的
But I think I got one to top this, and I'm really excited about this.
我要向大家介绍小肯吉
I want to introduce the world to little Kenzi, who was made by
由才华横溢的约・莫科斯小姐制作
a very talented artist by the name of Ms. Jo Moxy.
小肯吉配备齐全 上至黑色羽毛文胸
And little Kenzi's got everything from a black leather bra, to Lady
下至恨天高 完美发型和小手环
Gaga heals, and you know, the right hairdo, and the little cuffs.
而她马上会被慈善拍卖哦
And she's actually going to be auctioned off for charity.
希望你们中的一位不久会带着小肯吉回家
And so hopefully, one of you guys at home will have little Kenzi one day soon.
我不知道是不是最棒的
I don't know if I've got one to top that,
不过我也有件有意思的事
but I've got an interesting one.
显而易见的是 我们这剧有很多退伍的粉丝
Well, obviously, like the show has a lot of ex-military fans.
我们去亚特兰大的时候 我和一位粉丝
So when we were down in Atlanta, I had this really very, very
进行了长久深刻的交谈
deep conversation with this one fan.
她给我一枚硬币 她说要是你
So, she gave me this coin. So she said, if you meet anybody
遇见部队上的人 给他们看看硬币
in the military and you show them this coin, if they don't
要是他们没带硬币 依据军法 该请你喝酒
have their coin, they, by law, military law, have to buy you a drink.
- 什么?! - 上周我在纽约
- What?! - So I was in New York just last week.
有个妹子 超级可爱 而且是部队的人
This young girl, she was really lovely, and she was actually
她刚刚从阿富汗回来
in the military. She'd just come back from Afghanistan.
我口袋里刚好有那枚硬币 我想 我有招了
So I actually had it in my pocket. I thought, "I know I have that"
我从口袋掏出硬币 放在桌上
So I pulled it out of my jacket, I put it on the table.
她停下 跑到对街 一袋
She stopped, ran out, went across the street, came back with
- 啤酒买来 - 哇 真的假的?
- a brown paper bag with a beer - Oh! What?
- 放在我桌上 - 太赞了吧!
- inside of it and put it on my desk. - That was awesome!
- 毋庸置疑 - 真不错
- No questions asked. - That's nice.
- 挺酷的 - 确实不错
- That's cool. - That's pretty good, yeah.
可没那个酷
But it's not as cool as that.
Dv 潘德米克问 你怎么看塔米辛和波的
From DV Pandemic: "What is your view on the
化学反应和情侣关系?
chemistry/relationship between Tamsin and Bo?"
- 不存在 - 什么?
- It doesn't exist. - What?
我是说 我单纯爱你
I mean, I just love you.
很容易跟你来电
So it's so easy to have chemistry with you.
我感觉你就是那种人...
I feel that you're one of those people you know, where...
并不是我一人这样觉得
I didn't exclusively feel this.
我想遇见你的每个人都有这种感觉
I think everybody felt this way when they meet you.
就好像跟你认识好久了
Its like... you feel like you've known you forever.
- 哦 谢谢你 瑞秋- 你超级性感
- Oh, thank you, Rachel. - And you're hot.
- 锦上添花嘛 - 天啊
- So, that's cool. - Good Lord.
我觉得瑞秋和我之前有趣的是
What I think was interesting for Rachel and I, is that you
塔米辛和波开始就合不来
know, Tamsin and Bo didn't exactly hit it off
可是我们却很合得来
in the beginning, but Rachel and Anna did.
所以我们要强迫自己要记得
So we had to kind of remind ourselves that
我们恨对方 我们恨彼此
we hate each other, we hate each other.
- 我们本来很融洽 - 变脸 仇视彼此
- We'd be like, ha, ha, ha... - Yeah, hate each other.
没错 我想塔米辛和B相互尊重的
Exactly. But I think there is a mutual
她们是平等的
respect between Bo and Tamsin. They are equals.
她们都很强大
They are very powerful, so I think there is
我想其中既有化学反应又有尊重吧
a respect and the chemistry kind of exists there.
尽管她们可能意见相左
Even though they might not always love each other's
她们还是互相尊重
choices, they kind of respect them.
大伙们 我想知道
You know what I want to know, guys?
我想知道出演邪恶是什么感觉 禽兽伐克斯
I want to know what it's like to play the evil, monstrous Vex.
- 我就想知道这个 - 什么感觉
- That's what I want to know. - What is it like.
各种霸权集于一身什么感觉?
Yeah, what is it like to be the all-powerful Mesmer?
出演伐克斯 感觉太霸道了
It's like the most powerful thing ever, playing Vex,
每天都得穿皮裤
and just to be able to get into those leather pants every day
我走到片场 做那些手势
I come into set and just to do the hand movement.
没事了 没事了 一切都好的
It's okay. It's okay. Don't worry.
- 快看我的片段吧 - 好嘞
- Can we just watch me now? - Alright.
闭上眼 一秒钟 想想看
Close your peepers for one hot second and imagine this.
比查理・辛的自大还大的喷泉
Dulce de leche fountains big enough for Charlie Sheen's ego,
美味的宾客 让模特都蠢蠢欲动
guests so delicious, they'd make a model wanna eat.
还有一身行头 抢镜行头啊
And the outfits. Phwa! The outfits.
它们会让简-保罗 格烈丽的春款
They will make Jean-Paul Gaulthier's spring collection
看起来在重症监护室
look like a string-your-own macaroni necklace day
做出的意面项链 我们说的是
at the geriatric ward. Phew. We are talking about
世纪大趴 告别过去的我
the party of the century for little old "me."
聚光灯! 交响乐!
Spotlight! Symphony!
伐克斯 黑尔在一号线上
Vex, Hale is on line one.
他说这是他第七次打来了
He says it's the seventh time he tried to call you today.
可我很忙!
But I'm busy!
走进门来
Entrance.
全场瞩目于我 从血钻水晶吊饰灯下出场
All eyes on me as I descend on a blood diamond Chandelier.
事实上 他们倒下是因为你清除了他们
Fact: they descend cause that's how you clean them, apparently.
唏嘘 掌声
Gasps. Applause.
泪水 奖励
Tears. Boners.
迎接新黑暗时代的到来吧
Welcome to the start of the new Dark Era.
在节庆后 我的宾客们相要些小吃
Now, after the festivities, my guests will want some nosh.
此时你入场
And that's where you come in.
你是欧洲唯一一位愿意
Now, you are the only chef on the continent
准备河豚的大厨
that is willing to prepare Fugu, the cyanide of fish.
准备不当 会立刻致命
Prepared incorrectly, it will kill, instantly.
好了 为什么你的证书是无效的?
Now. Why have all your references been crossed off?
艾尔莎!
Alyssa!
能为您效劳吗?
What can I do for you?
试试河豚
Uh, try the Fugu.
- 我食素 - 噢 素食主义者啊
- I'm vegan. - "Oh, I'm vegan"!
哦 看在我们最爱的歌手 王子的份上
Oh! For the love of the artist formerly known as Prince,
跟我说你定了地点
tell me you booked the venue.
是的 其实他们刚...
Yeah. Actually, they just got back...
敢告诉我坏消息试试!
Don't you dare think about giving me bad news!
因为别墅是政府财产
Since the chateau is part government property,
他们要求申请 并要几个月才能通过
they require an application and the process takes months.
那B计划呢 游船趴?
What about plan B, the party boat?
我知道不同寻常 可我们别无他法啊
I mean, I know it's a tad common, but it's the only choice we got left.
港口法律规定夜间九点以后严禁喧哗音乐
The harbour laws have restrictions on loud music after 9:00 P.M.
宾客数量也有严格限制
and restrictions on numbers of guests.
我们不能招待一千五百人 需要许可
We can't accommodate 1500 people. It would require a permit.
- 将需要... - 让我猜猜!
- That would take... - Let me guess!
- 几个月通过? - 没错
- Months? - Yeah.
办个派对能有多难?!
How hard is it to arrange a party?!
你想要我吗 伐克斯?
Yeah, is that what you want, Vex?
今天免了 小甜心
Not today, sugar puffs.
你说噎死不算亲热
You said choking isn't making out.
是啊 可是你激怒我了
Yeah, but you've made me very upset.
这个派对就是一切
This party is everything,
而就我在打理一切
and I feel like I'm doing all the work.
一人的把戏!
A bloody one-man show!
我喜欢一个人的表演只有洗澡
And the only one-man show I fancy is a long shower in chaps, yeah?
- 要我给你洗澡吗? - 不必
- Should I start the shower for you? - Negative.
我会另找地点 有泳池 旋转楼梯
I'll find you another venue, and it'll be even better with a pool
以备你的华丽登场
and a winding staircase for your grand entrances.
那华丽的告别呢?
How about a grand exit?
试试鱼吧
Try... the... fish.
去你的 你有工作了
Fug you. You're hired...
前提是找到场地 嘿 你 下一位!
providing we can find a venue. Hey, you, next!
嘿
Hello.
有什么能为您效劳?
What can I do for you?
亲爱的 说话用中气
You'll have to use your outside voice, darling.
- 叫什么名字? - 贝蒂
- What's your name? - Betty.
很好 艾尔莎 我现在想办个派对
Oh, perfect, Alyssa. Now, I simply am trying to throw a party.
可我总是碰到阻拦
But I keep running into red tape.
现在我要你把一切阻碍消灭
Now I'd like you to make that red tape vanish.
我可不想听到失败的消息
And if it's still there, I don't wanna hear anything about it
你的工作就是想尽一切办法
because it's your job to find a way
让它成功的 明白?
around it. Got it?
哦...
Ohh...
真是个苦差事 亲爱的
It's hard work, darling.
我是说 各种束缚和无能的人
I mean, restrictions, incompetent people.
我就只想办个派对啊
And I'm just simply trying to throw a party.
那我要想干大事了可怎么办?
What's gonna happen when I try to do something serious?
- 我到底做了什么? - 包裹?
- What have I done? - Package?
好吧 令人印象深刻 我懂
Oh, yeah. It's impressive, I know.
在澳大利亚 他们叫这个便当
In Australia, they call this a "packed lunch."
- 放桌上就行了 - 好的
- You can just put it on the desk. - Okay.
- 要放映机吗? - 速速取来
- Projector? - Quickly.
杀了厨子 派对结束了
And kill the caterer. The party is over.
- 噢 - 你穿皮裤真好看 保罗
- Ooh. - You do look good in leather, Paul.
有趣的是 我当时是一镜到底
The funny thing about that is I actually do that all in one,
每次都如此 太难了
every single time, which is pretty tricky.
- 一身劲装啊! - 很难 没有别的意思
- That's an outfit! - Tricky. No pun intended.
很大程度上是因为... 是的 没错
It's largely because... Yeah, exactly.
很大程度上是因为我是
It's largely because I am the
我们之中唯一一位科班出身的演员
only classical trained actor amongst us all.
- 对吗? - 你倒还真敢说
- Is this correct? - You gotta lay that on.
好了 马上回来更多妖女迷行主创精彩
Anyway, we'll be back soon with more from the Lost Girl cast.
不要走开
Stay tuned.
嗨 我是瑞秋・司德腾 欢迎回来俱乐部
Hi. I'm Rachel Skarsten, and we are back in the Clubhouse.
再过几分钟就是第四季首映啦
We're minutes away from the premiere,
让我们看看粉丝提问
so let's get right back to our fans.
问题来自亚历山大・德赛 请补充这句话
This one is from Alexandra Desan. "Finish this sentence:
- 这一季更... - 史诗巨著
- "This season is more..." - Epic.
小偷! 我本来要说这个的
Oh, you stealer! That's what I was going to say.
更魔幻 更戏剧化
Magical. Theatrical.
有点颠覆你的猜测
It's more of the opposite of what you think you know.
- 没错 出乎意料 - 更左倾一点
- Yeah, it's more like that. - It's a lot more left than right.
- 是的 - 前所未有的大范围
- Yes. - It's more circular than it's ever been.
- 有些缺少中心 - 更高了
- It's more less centre. - It's taller.
- 太疯狂了 - 范围更宽
- It's bananas. - It's a little wider.
- 更多独角兽了 - 有时它们会躺下
- It's more unicorn. - Sometimes it lies down.
- 它们肌肉发达 - 有时还唱歌
- It's hefty. - Occasionally it sings.
好了 下个问题 很好 谢谢你
Okay, next question. Great. Thank you.
祖伊・巴莫
Zoie Palmer.
这是比利・麦克西向大伙的提问
This is from Billy McCarthy for everyone.
如何平衡你们的个人生活和职业生活呢?
"What is it like balancing your personal lives and your professional lives?"
我们生活在这 我们在这住
Ooh. We live here. We live,
在这呼吸 流汗流泪
breathe, sweat and cry here.
就像是我们第二个家
This is kind of like our second family.
可是我想我们真的家人很想念我们
But I think our real families do miss us.
很有意思 因为我们是演员
It's interesting, because when we work as actors, there is
所以常常就会有所扮演角色和本人
a lot of transference sometimes between the character that we
之间的转换问题 可是我发现司凯乐
play and the person that we are. But I have found with Skyler,
每次我见司凯乐 他都不一样
whenever I see Skyler, there is a wash, a clean wash.
我想做一个好人
And it's just like I want to be the best
我想当他的好父亲
person I can be, the best dad I can be for him.
这就是柯辛娜和我对马科斯和缇娜的感觉
That's how Ksenia and I feel about Max and Tina.
我们为了他们成为更好的人
We just want to be the best people we can be for them.
快乐 并爱着他们
Happy. Yeah, and love them.
喂他们最好的粮食
Feed them the best Kibble.
- 最好的粮食 - 好好将他们养大
- The best Kibble. - Train them properly.
- 说得好 瑞秋- 说实话 我们
- That's beautiful, Rachel. - Honestly, we have a pretty
妖女迷行是个很棒的大家庭 你们也都看到了
amazing family at Lost Girl, which you can see.
有时真的超级好笑
Sometimes things get pretty hilarious.
- 搞笑 - 让我们看看一些瞬间
- Hilarious. - Let's take a look at some
我们中有些人不好过哦
moments that didn't go too well for a couple of us.
天啊
Oh, my god.
开拍!
Action!
我跟黑暗小精灵握手言和
So I shook hands with a dark pixie
如今我欠你了我欠你?
and now I owe you my IOU?
是啊  没错
Yeah. Uh-uh. Exactly.
你该剪头了 抱歉
You deserve a haircut. Whoops.
我刚刚打到克里斯的球了
I just hit Kris in the balls.
让我们从踢球那里开始 我爱被虐
Let's pick it up from the ball hit. Because I like that so much.
说真的 你是什么?
Seriously, what are you?
你永远杀不死我的 波波
Something you can't kill, Bo-Bo.
这个也许会杀了你哦
But this might kill you.
停!
Cut!
我很抱歉 不好意思了 各位
I'm so sorry. Sorry, guys.
有人干扰我的魔力
Somebody's f . . . -ing with my magic.
- 太棒了 - 太有了
- That was awesome. - That was the way to go.
- 看这个真不错 - 谢谢你们邀请我
- That was good to see. - Thank you very much for having me.
我要去赶飞机啦
I have to go to make a flight.
不过其他人还会陪大家
But everyone else will be back very soon. Mwah!
- 爱你哦 - 拜!
- Love you. - Bye!
大家好 我是祖伊・巴莫欢迎回到俱乐部
Hi, hello. I'm Zoie Palmer. Welcome back to the Clubhouse.
我真的吃爆米花就停不下来
I literally can't stop eating popcorn.
这是我第七盒了
I'm on my seventh box of popcorn here.
第四季马上首映开始 我们好激动啊
The season 4 premiere is coming up very soon. We're all very excited.
不过还有些时间回答粉丝问题
But we still have some time for some more fan questions.
安吉拉・罗曼提问
This one is from Angela Romano.
我们还会看到肯吉和劳伦曾经的故事吗?
"Will we learn more about Kenzi and Lauren's back story?"
- 哦 - 你是随机抽到那个的吗?
- Oh. - Did you pull that one by accident?
- 你从哪拿的? - 关于我的啊
- Where did you get that? - Anything about me.
我想是的 我们确实更了解劳伦了
I think that, yes, we do learn more about Lauren's back story.
我们了解更多她的毛病是什么
We'll learn a little bit more about what her problem is.
我不知道 你说呢肯吉?
And I don't know, what about you, Kenz?
我想是的 我们探讨了肯吉的过去
I think, yeah, we delve into Kenzi's past and some peeps
看见些事 不会剧透太多 有人
appear, without giving too much away, who kind of shed
让肯吉的人生增光添色 还有她的家乡
some light on Kenzi's life and where she comes from.
好了 又到视频提问环节
Okay. We are going to go on to a video question.
我们看大屏幕吧
We're gonna watch the monitor.
嗨 我是安娜 我的问题是 肯吉和劳伦
Hi, I'm Anna. My question is, will Kenzi and
还是朋友吗? 我希望如此
Lauren be friends this season? I hope so.
她说"肯吉和劳伦这一季还是朋友吗?"
She said, "Will Kenzi and Lauren be friends this season?"
- 我希望如此 - 天啊
- I hope so. - Oh my god.
在第三季终时 我们终于
Well, at the end of season 3, we finally, you know,
冰释前嫌 聊开了
dish it out, talk things out.
是啊 我们拍了那场
Yeah, we had that scene
那时我们都有点暴脾气 之后...
where we were a bit grumpy and then we got...
- 更发火了 - 记得暴脾气那场吗?
- Very grumpy. - Remember that grumpy scene?
- 我们一起打猪 - 是啊
- We fought pigs together. - Yeah.
记得吗? 那很好啊
Remember that? That was nice.
- 我感觉... - 我们快了
- So I feel like, you know... - We're getting there.
我们有了我们的愤怒时间
We've had our grumpy, mean times.
所以是时候让肯吉和劳伦相亲相爱了
I feel like it's time to get in to the love with Kenzi and Lauren.
好了 到了网络片段的时间
Okay, now it's webisode time.
今年我们会介绍一种全新异种
And we're introducing a whole other kind of Fae this year.
我们在参加会议时有过暗示
And we've hinted about that at some of our conventions that we've attended.
现在是时候更多了解今年异种世界
But now it's time to get to know a little more about some of the
异种世界的新人了
new players in the Fae world this year.
或者说 一些老演员
Or rather, some of the old players.
异种电影公司荣誉出品:
The Faedonia Film Company presents:
逐步了解你
Getting to Know You
第二章: 尤那达人
Chapter 2: The Una Mens
又见面啦
Oh. Well, hello again.
是我 你们的老伙伴 弗兰林・德克
It's me, your old pal, Flynn Decker.
希望你们喜欢上周的"逐步了解你"
I so hope you enjoyed last week's presentation of Getting
第一章 血圣的消失
to Know You, chapter one, The Disappearance of the Bloody King.
这将我们引向新物种 尤那达人
Which of course brings us to the creation of the Una Mens.
他们是谁? 做什么事?
Who are they? What do they do?
对你我又意味着什么呢?
What do they mean to you or I?
我会详细告诉你的
Well, I'll tell you sure enough.
我们何不先去看看
But why don't we first find out what
你已知的 并从那开始吧
you know already and go from there.
他们不在这 对吧 强尼?
They're not here, are they, Johnny?
嘿 问你呢 谁是尤那达人?
Hey, you there, who are the Una Mens?
我听说他们是超级英雄 这样就能把你灭了
I heard they were superheroes and they could wipe you out just like that.
左勾拳 右勾拳 你挂了
Wham, smack, pow, bam!
你个子挺低的 胆子倒挺大
You're short, buzz, but not on moxie.
- 我听说他们是大妖怪 - 噢!
- I heard they was the bogeymens. - Aw!
不 小姑娘对不住了 那是吾那达人
Oh, no, sorry little one, that's Una Mens.
看来我们需要点帮助啊
Hmm. Well, it looks like we're gonna need a little help.
尤那达人是古种生物 是异种长老
The Una Mens are near Omiscient,in fact they are fae elders
他们解决问题 践行法律 执行死刑
who solve problems doing enforce the laws and pin the death.
懂了么?
Easy enough for you?
尤那达人掠走了我的孩子 我的儿子!
The Una Mens took my son. My boy!
我要他们死光!
And I want them dead!
要是你问我 他们就该被吊死
If you ask me, they should be strung up, brought to the
被恐吓 用尽一切办法折磨
gallows and whooped but good! Ah!
不不!
No! No!
坏了
Uh-oh.
看来有人忘了尤那达人的三R定律了
It looks like somebody forgot the three R's of the Una Mens:
自律 自尊 自醒
restraint, respect, or reckoning.
一切都很简单  对于异种世界里
It's all quite simple, really. There's nothing to fear for the
遵纪守法的公民来说没什么害怕的
law-abiding citizens of the Fae world.
我们要保持冷静 拼搏向前
We must keep calm and carry on.
并且铭记 如果我们尊重
And remember, if we show
并受异种法律约束
restraint and respect the laws
就不会有...
of the Fae, there will be no...
不会有... 喂!
no... Psst!
- 巴兹 该说台词了 - 没有自醒
- Buzz, that's your cue. - No reckoning.
接得好 小伙 有此光明异种的态度
Nice one, junior. Why, with a nice Light Fae
有朝一日你可能当阿什哦
attitude like that, you're a shoo-in for Ash one day.
也许可以演阿什
Oh. Well, maybe acting Ash.
为什么 我应...
Why, I outta...!
悠着点 小伙 记住 偏离法律
Easy, junior. Remember, stray from the one
或者说强纳森太太的感恩节
true set of laws, and, well, let's just say Mrs. Johnson's
火鸡就会变小不少哦
turkey is gonna be a little bit smaller this Thanksgiving.
- 去死吧 - 拜托 强纳森太太
- Go to hell! - Oh, come now, Mrs. Johnson,
我们要明白尤那达人的三R法则
we all must observe the 3 R's of the Una Mens.
没有了他们 就没有了灾难
For without them, there would be chaos.
没人愿意那样的
And nobody wants that.
所以 朋友们 对于诚实守信的
So you see, friends, life as
异种而言 生活就是...
an honest to goodness Fae is...
简单来说...
It's as easy as 1...
It's as easy as...
自律
restraint.
我做不下去了
I can't do this anymore. This...
这他妈到底是什么?
what the hell is this, huh?
死亡异种之书吗?
Is this the book of dead Fae?
还有死亡异种的照片
There's pictures of dead Fae in here.
他们想怎么样...
What, do they... Do they do what...
你干的?
So you do this?
我认识这些人
I know some of these people.
什么 我是下一个吗?
What, am I next?
我有消息给你 哥们 你不能杀我
Well, I got news for you, pal. You can't have me.
因为我只听命于弗兰林・德克
'Cause I only answer to Flynn Decker, and Flynn Decker only.
把你手放开! 不! 不!
Take your hands off...! No. No!
不!
No!
- 好赞啊 - 太诡异了
- That was awesome, eh? - Creepy.
- 有点吓人 - 我们越来越接近
- And a little terrifying. - We're getting closer to the
首映时间啦 不要走开哦
premiere of Lost Girl, so do not go anywhere.
好了 各位 欢迎回来俱乐部
All right, guys, welcome back to the Clubhouse.
我们都很激动 不能自已啦
We are so excited, we can't even contain ourselves, because you
因为你们马上就要看到第四季第一集啦
guys are about to see the season 4 premiere. Okay?
在那之前 还有些
So, just before we do that, we're going to get a couple more
粉丝提问需要回答 好吗?
fan questions in before we go. All right?
不许再吃爆米花啦 箱子拿来
So enough popcorn. Hand over the box.
好啦!
All right!
来自布丽・安柏・尤曼的问题 问祖伊
This is from Bri Amber "Yumans"? Okay. This is for Zoie.
亲爱的 问题是为了扮演劳伦
And the question is, my love: "Was it hard learning
学习那么多医用术语很难吗?
all those medical terms and phrases Lauren says?
那其他人呢? 如何为角色准备的?
How about everyone else? How do you prepare for scenes?"
是的 很难 非常难
Yes, it's hard. It is hard.
我有时根本不懂我在说什么
I sometimes have no idea what I'm saying.
我真的只记发音然后背出来的
I literally just memorize it phonetically and then say it.
- 其他人呢? - 我绝对谷歌了
- How about everyone else? - I definitely Google and
并且维基百科了异种什么的 因为...
Wikipedia different Fae stuff. And because it's...
是啊 我需要脑袋里有画面
Yeah. I need to have a picture of something in my head
才能诠释故事嘛
when I'm trying to tell you guys a story.
我在片场乱转 在角落乱闻 在东西上乱尿
I walk on set, I smell in corners, I pee on things.
还冲陌生人乱吼
And I just kind of basically growl at the odd stranger.
舔自己的蛋蛋
And you lick your own balls.
好吧 那可得几年瑜伽功夫呢 哥们
Yes. Well, that took years of yoga, Paul.
不要低估我的训练
Don't diminish my training.
来到这 上妆发 装尾巴
Getting here and then going into the hair and make-up
就是我们常做的第一件事
trailer, which is usually the first thing that we do.
我开始逐渐觉得我越来越像波
I slowly start to feel more and more like Bo.
我一穿上紧裤子 就有裂纹
And then as soon as I put on the tight pants a
又搭皮带什么的...
nd the cleavage comes out and the belt goes on...
- 而且安娜就走掉了 - 安娜转头就走
- And the Anna goes away! - The Anna goes away.
我是谁啊? 不 我是说...
Who am I? No. I mean, it's...
我真的感觉我准备好一展身手了
And then I really feel ready to kick some ass.
我想知道你们在家什么感觉 知道再过
I wonder how you guys at home are feeling, knowing that we are
一会 史诗般的第四季就要拉开帷幕啦
mere moments away from the epic season 4 premiere.
马上播出 再回答一个问题
We are this close, but we've got one more question.
- 这是最终特别问题 - 好激动
- So this is the special last question. - Exciting.
我要去拿异种盒子 抽出题来
I'm gonna reach into the Fae box and I'm gonna pull it out.
来自简宁斯・肖恩的问题
And the question is from Janice Shawn.
我们知道你们不能剧透第四季
"We know you can't give away season 4,
不过给点线索吧
but throw us a bone."
- 噢! - 天啊!
- Ohh! - Gosh!
哇喔!
Whoa!
谈论第四季太难了 因为
It is so hard to talk about season 4, because there were
第三季留了很多悬念
so many cliff-hangers at the end of season 3.
不过我可以保证 你不会失望
Yeah. I can say I do feel like you won't be disappointed.
- 绝不会失望 - 你绝对不会失望
- Will not be disappointed. - You will not be disappointed.
- 火力全开的一季 - 太多转折
- It's a strong season. - There are so many twists and
峰回路转 迷雾重重 秘密勾当 性感撩人
turns and mysteries and secrets and sexiness.
我想每个角色 你都会
And I think each of the characters, you're going to see
以前所未有的角度审视他们
them in a way you've never quite seen them before.
- 我觉得这对我们都适用 - 没错
- And I think that is the case for all of us. - Yeah, that's true.
我想我们中的每位你都将会
I don't think there is any one of us that you're not going to get
有更进一步的了解 也会有更多惊喜
to know a little bit more about, and it will be a bit of a surprise.
- 是啊 - 等不及听听你们的观后感啦
- Yeah. - We can't wait to hear what you guys think.
我相信我们会很快再跟大家聊天的
I'm sure we will talk to you guys very soon.
- 我们希望你们会喜欢哦 - 太棒了!
- We hope you love it. - Yes!
这一季有大场面 有大邪恶 现在就为您呈现
This season got big, it got bad. We're going to bring it to you right now.
- 是的 没错 - 耶
- Yes, we are. - Yeah.
十分感谢粉丝们的提问
And thank you very much to all of our fans
我们今晚都学到很多
for great questions. We all learned a lot tonight.
我们拍第四季时都相当愉快
And we had a great time filming season 4.
是的 没错
Yes, we did.
我们由衷希望你们会喜欢哦
And we really hope that you all enjoy it.
几秒钟后就会首播 不要走开
It's coming up in just a few seconds, so don't go anywhere.
- 再见 各位 - 再见!
- Bye, everyone. - Bye!
- 我爱你们! - 哒哒
- I love you! - Ta-ta.
亲亲! 永远的好朋友!
Mwah! Best friends ever!